<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--Generated by crowdin.com-->
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2018. Jahir Fiquitiva
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the CreativeCommons Attribution-ShareAlike
  ~ 4.0 International License. You may not use this file except in compliance
  ~ with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~    http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/legalcode
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    <string name="coming_soon">În curând</string>
    <!-- List Of Drawer Sections -->
    <string name="section_home">Acasă</string>
    <string name="section_icons">Pictograme</string>
    <string name="section_apply">Aplică</string>
    <string name="section_wallpapers">Fundaluri</string>
    <string name="section_icon_request">Cerere de pictograme noi</string>
    <string name="section_donate">Donează</string>
    <string name="section_about">Despre</string>
    <string name="section_help">Ajutor</string>
    <string name="section_zooper">Setări Zooper</string>
    <string name="section_widgets">Widget-uri</string>
    <string name="share_this_app">Recomand %1$s. %2$s</string>
    <string name="rate">Evaluează</string>
    <!-- Icons filters -->
    <string name="filter">Filtru</string>
    <string name="clear">Șterge</string>
    <string name="more_apps">Mai multe aplicații</string>
    <string name="general_info">Informații generale</string>
    <string name="useful_links">Link-uri utile</string>
    <string name="columns">Număr de coloane</string>
    <string name="lni_content">%1$s nu este instalat.\nDescarc din Play Store?</string>
    <string name="no_compatible_launcher_title">Acest ecran principal NU este compatbil</string>
    <!-- Widgets Names -->
    <string name="iconrestorer_widget_title">Reactivează pictograma</string>
    <string name="clock_widget_title">Ceas analogic</string>
    <string name="search_icons">Caută pictograme</string>
    <string name="search_wallpapers">Caută fundaluri</string>
    <string name="search_launchers">Caută ecrane principale</string>
    <string name="search_apps">Caută aplicații</string>
    <string name="seconds">Secunde</string>
    <string name="minutes">Minute</string>
    <string name="hours">Ore</string>
    <string name="days">Zile</string>
    <string name="weeks">Săptămâni</string>
    <string name="months">Luni</string>
    <!-- Requests -->
    <string name="select_all">Selectare toate</string>
    <string name="no_selected_apps_title">Nicio aplicație selectată</string>
    <!-- Preferences -->
    <!-- HELP SECTION -->
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>How to use the Icon Pack?</item>
        <item>How to apply the Icon Pack?</item>
        <item>How to see all the included icons?</item>
        <item>How to replace an icon with an alternative one?</item>
        <item>How to request unthemed icons?</item>
        <item>After restarting my device, icon pack is not applied anymore. Icons were restored to default.</item>
        <item>Why do icons look pixelated on my device?</item>
        <item>I can see an icon for X app in the included icons, but the icon does not apply.</item>
        <item>How to hide app icon from launcher?</item>
        <item>How to open the app after app icon is hidden from launcher?</item>
        <item>How to show app icon in launcher again?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to modify or delete content of my storage?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to full network access?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to view connections?</item>
        <item>De ce aplicația cere permisiune pentru a aplica fundaluri?</item>
        <item>De ce aplicația cere permisiune pentru a ajusta dimensiunile?</item>
        <item>Why does the app need permission to prevent phone from sleeping?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>You need a launcher with icon packs support. The list of supported launchers might be found in the app in the \"Apply\" section, or Play Store description.</item>
        <item>Depending on the app\'s navigation type, you need to either slide the navigation drawer from the left, and go to \"Apply\" section, or choose 4th icon from the bottom navigation bar. From there you can choose a launcher you want to apply the icons to. Some launchers doesn\'t support auto-applying and you have to do it manually through their settings.</item>
        <item>Go back to main section of the app and tap the tile titled \"Icons\".</item>
        <item>Depending on the launcher you\'re using, you either have to long tap the icon and select \"Edit\" from the pop-up menu, or long tap the icon and move it to a \"Edit\" box.</item>
        <item>Depending on the app\'s navigation type, you need to either slide the navigation drawer from the left, and go to \"Requests\" section, or choose the icon from the bottom navigation bar.</item>
        <item>S-a întâmplat deoarece aplicația a fost instalată pe cardul SD. Instalați aplicația în memoria internă.</item>
        <item>The problem might come with the launcher you are using, when handling big resolution. You can fix it by increasing icon size to 115 – 120%. Or try using another launcher.</item>
        <item>Trimite o cerere de pictograme.</item>
        <item>Slide the NavigationDrawer from the left, or tap the 3-dot menu button and go to \"Settings\" section. Then check the \"Hide icon from launcher\" option.</item>
        <item>Go to your home screen, then create a widget for the app which name is \"IconRestorer\" and tap it.</item>
        <item>Slide the NavigationDrawer from the left, or tap the 3-dot menu button and go to \"Settings\" section. Then uncheck the \"Hide icon from launcher\" option.</item>
        <item>It\'s needed to be able write icon requests data and files, as well as saving wallpapers, and being able to change Wallpapers\' download location.</item>
        <item>It\'s needed to be able to load wallpapers from cloud and download them.</item>
        <item>Este necesar pentru verificarea conexiunii la internet.</item>
        <item>Este necesar pentru a seta un fundal direct din aplicație.</item>
        <item>Este necesar pentru a putea ajusta fundalul în funcție de rezoluția ecranului tău.</item>
        <item>Este necesar pentru Muzei Live Wallpaper.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
